♪ BGM
Wow!
Good morning!
Today is one-one live! Let's do our best! Let's do our best!
Looking forward to it! Looking forward to it!
Hello! Here's something for you.
Thank you very much.
Mina-chan, you always teach us fruits.
Yes!
Yay!
Good morning.
I'm here, please.
Yay!
Bon appétit.
Good morning
What's this?
Egg...
Good morning!
Good morning, Sue!
Bon appétit!
I'm stuffed!
Strawberries are the best!
Today I'm doing a one-man show at ZEPP Shinjuku!
My first time at ZEPP!
I'm really looking forward to it!
Thank you very much!
It's gone!
Thank you very much.
No, no, no, why.
I mean, you know,
It looked like fun.
Yeah.
Oh, I'm out.
I totally get it!
Hey! You, don't run away.
Hey!
It says "perturbed" on it.
Yeah.
You, again,
I'm going to have a beef bowl in the morning.
You never know who ate the beef bowl.
LOL!
Red! Red! Red! Red!
Oh, man!
I'm in the rebellious phase of my life.
What was that? Junior high? High school?
Sixth grade.
Sixth grade and you're already wearing it.
You used to follow my lead.
Yes, I did.
I did my makeup today.
Your hair is like Newgins' springy hair.
The usual.
Like on stage.
I couldn't do it if I didn't have it done.
I couldn't do it otherwise.
And here's a braid.
For those of you who are like that, the Shine Muscat is
I want it! Yay!
So from Yuna-chan
that she gave me my muscat.
Today.
Really.
It's the first time I'm getting rave reviews.
Everyone is already from the front to the back
Everyone from the front to the back to the top
I'm shaking! I don't know if it's going to be
I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to
I can make it sound
I'll try to make it ring.
So that when people leave, they'll think it was fun.
I want to do my best
I'll do my best!
When I was at the VLOG in Tochigi
I sang "Prime Numbers" at the VLOG in Tochigi.
And it was
It was on the air.
No way!
Prime Numbers
Toot-toot.
It was a spoiler.
Did you notice?
I don't know.
So, well...
Try it twice.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Sleepy-sleepy-sleepy-sleepy-sleepy.
Sleepy-sleepy-sleepy-sleepy-sleepy-sleepy.
That's a real wow factor.
It's Wanmiyan Live today.
There's a sparkle under my eyes
Yay!
It's not so easy for boys
Our members don't do it.
I heard you checked with the manager.
If it's okay...
I'm sure you'll like it differently than usual.
Anri
Anri's hand
Yes, it is.
I don't know, until last time, in the rehearsal...
but this time
We started from the point of what we should do to make a good product.
We talked about how to make it better.
And of course, we
Of course, we have a lot of opinions
And of course, we included a lot of our opinions
And through that
We also got advice from the teachers and so on.
So I feel like we've made it up as we went along.
I feel like I've made it all up as I go along.
But when it comes to the actual performance
Because everyone's passion is so strong
It's hard to really feel it, isn't it?
Hire work
It's overwhelming.
Hire work and overwhelming.
That's it.
On my count.
Together.
I want to go through the whole song.
I want to go all the way.
Make-up
I'm done.
I usually...
I usually curl my hair.
but this time I'm wearing it straight.
Yay!
We are One Love One Heart!
We are One Love One Heart, please rehearse!
Please rehearse with us!
Fireworks, are you in?
4?
Four? One.
It's okay.
It's just enough to get the man of shame in.
Where is it? I want you to stand up for once. Fireworks.
Side one.
Isshin's a little too far out.
Maybe a little more to the right.
Mr. Jesus?
Or the family chairman.
Oh, but we'll do all the work.
Okay, beautiful.
Just the rehearsals, just a little bit, because Amu's coming this way.
Okay, okay.
Okay, okay, okay.
Love you, Shikoku, for we've had a rough day
Even if you know when it's coming to an end
(Let's love them, even if they run their mouths and everything)
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
I love you, I love you, I love you
Hey! Don't run away! Don't run away! You're out of rehearsal!
How's your day going? Hey! Listen to me!
What is it? It's a presentation! No, it's not! Is that the game?
Aah! Aah! I'm in! Haruma's not in it!
He did it the other day! Oh, yeah! I'm going to put on my makeup too!
Okay, I'm going to go do my makeup!
Thank you for watching!
Well, well, well...
I'm getting a feel for it in rehearsal.
It's going to be a great show!
Thank you very much.
It's like this.
As we get closer to the rehearsal
I sometimes get tense.
I'm just...
I'll try my best to keep up the tension.
Let's go for it!
I'm doing well.
I'm doing good.
You're doing great.
That's the voice of ten.
The voice of ten
Warabi-mochi
I love warabimochi!
Let's go.
I can't see.
More than you think.
Ears! Ears!
I can't see.
No, no, no, no, no.
One, two, three, four.
Oh, I got it, I got it.
Oh!
Let's go again.
One, two, three, four.
Yay, yay, yay.
Okay, thank you very much.
We did great.
It was a very high wall.
I mean, it was a sold-out event.
I'm so glad that we've been able to do this.
I'm very grateful to have been able to welcome you
I am very grateful for this opportunity.
I would be very happy if I could repay everyone on this stage.
The lead song of the album is "Aisegorosanzan no uso no cost".
The lyrics are really good.
If you pay attention to the lyrics and listen to it
If you pay attention to the lyrics, you'll find that they will bring tears to your eyes.
Please give it a listen!
We have many new songs.
We have many new songs, so rather than getting excited with the audience at Two Boom
We have a lot of things for the audience to see this time, so we will put a lot of attention into each song.
We put a lot of attention into each song.
We have received songs of various genres and atmospheres for each song, so we will deliver them to you one by one.
I want to deliver them one by one to the audience.
I'd like to do it with that in mind.
We want to show our male side the most.
We want to show our male side.
We want to show that we are not limited to this box.
We would like you to fill it with our thoughts that we are not going to stop at this box.
I'm finally starting to get a sense of what it's like.
I'm getting a little nervous.
I hope I can give a good performance as usual.
I've been summoned to the assembly, so I'm off.
We're not the kind of people who stop here, are we?
What about our goal?
Tokyo Dome.
We'll accelerate from here.
I hope we can take even one step forward.
All we can do is have fun!
Are you all fired up?
Let's be as one!
Wear! Wonder for hearts!
Okay, okay, okay, go for it!
Good luck.
Chocolate, right?
No.
Metal.
Let's go.
What do you say you and I hug it out?
You wanna give me a hug?
Yeah. - Yeah.
I'm ready.
You're good.
Three, two, one.
Oh oh oh oh
We are
One love one heart
We are ONE LOVE ONE HEART
Let's go
Let's go Hibi Kowake Hibi Kowake Hibi Kowake Seriously, Choo Choo Choo Choo Choo Choo
Let's go, day by day, day by day, day by day, day by day, seriously, Choo Choo Choo Choo Choo Choo Choo
Progression of drainage Step line Start line Seriously can't get enough of it
To be the best everyday
Our fan name will be announced today!
So we'd like to announce it!
Here is our fan name!
Lovato!
My name is Lovato!
I took the love and the heart from "One Lavato"...
and then we just clunked it together.
GACHANKO!
It's called "Lavato"!
At first glance, you see, what is Lavato?
What the heck is that? at first glance, you may wonder what it is.
Please remember it!
Yay!
Thank you for watching!
First of all, thank you so much for the sold-art tickets today.
Thank you very much.
This venue, filled with people, is something that we couldn't have seen on our own.
We couldn't have done it by ourselves.
This one-man show is a challenge.
We knew that if we didn't get through this one-man show, we wouldn't get to where we wanted to go.
If we don't overcome this challenge, we won't be able to go beyond it.
That's why we often felt impatient.
We always felt anxious.
We always had a sense of anxiety somewhere in our hearts.
There were times when I dreaded the day of January 8th.
But in the midst of all this
I had a chance to meet you all
I had a chance to talk directly with you all
I'm sure we'll do it with Solder.
Thank you very much for watching.
Every single word that you've said to us...
You've been by our side, and you've helped us to face this great challenge.
I'd like to thank my second family, the members of this group and the staff.
Everyone at Lovato.
I love One Love One Heart that we make with these members.
There are so many groups in the world.
Love One.
I'm so glad that you found Love One.
and
Thank you so much for supporting Love One
Thank you very much!
As Love One with no limits in 2024
I would like to continue to run through the year 2024 with these 9 members and all LOVERs.
Thank you very much for coming to FIFTH ONE MAN LIVE SKY'S A LIMIT ZEPP Shinjuku today.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
This one-man show is
Last fours one-man live was
It was pretty much just us.
It ended up being a lot of fun for me, but this time
But this time, I was able to enjoy myself while thinking about the audience.
I was able to enjoy myself while thinking about the audience
I'm happy about that.
I think I gave it my all.
ZEPP Shinjuku is a great place for us
ZEPP Shinjuku is a very high wall for us
I didn't know if we could get over it.
We didn't know if we could get over it at first.
But with the help of Rubber and everyone else, we were able to make it to the hottest venue in the world.
I think we were able to make it the hottest venue in the world.
I really think it was a lot of fun.
It was really fun.
Thank you so much!
It all happened so fast.
I was like, "Did I just perform? It was like...
I don't feel like it's over yet.
I don't feel like I've started or finished.
I know, I know.
But it was a great day.
I really want to go further and further in 2024.
I really want to go even higher and higher
Today, I was reminded of that.
The moment I stepped out on stage, I saw the view...
There is the back of the stage! It's so wide! I thought.
Everyone was already waving their penlights.
The view was so beautiful!
The beginning of the year 2024 has already become the best
I'm so happy.
I felt like I could see a wider view with One Love One Heart.
I thought that I could see a wider view with one love one heart.
I'm going to do my best!
I finally decided on a fan name and
and I was able to announce it.
I'd like to reaffirm that I don't have a fan name, but I'd like to use it in the form of everyone who supports me.
But I would like to deliver my words to all of you who support me.
I'd like to say thank you to all of you who have been supporting me.
I've had the opportunity to meet with them.
But now, with the start of 2024, we are going to make a full-fledged effort to
I would like to take this opportunity to make a step forward with the Lovato people
I think this is the first step for us to take together.
I think today was a big day for us to announce Lavato.
I think today was a very big day for us.
Let's go to the front of the stage.
Where am I?
I'm going in.
Let's go to the front of the stage.
Okay, okay, here we go.
When I say I'm on stage.
I said, "I'm on the happy stage.
I say, "OK, OK, I'm happy.
I'll go to the front of the stage too.
Thank you very much.
I'm on stage!
When you get on stage...
I'll let you know when we're done.
Happy stage!
cry of stage
We did it!
Yes!
Now, now, now, full shot!
Wait!
Okay, let's do it.
Ready?
Whoo!
Yeah!
- Look happy! - So happy!
We've been planning this for three months.
- I've been working on it for a month! - We've been working on it for 3 months!
- Gentlemen! - So happy!
Bite down on the top!
Go get your essay, huh?
- Wow! - Wow! You look happy!
You look happy!
I love shortcake!
Let's take a picture of it as it is.
You can eat whatever you want.
You can stick your face on it.
You should stick your face to it.
Wait a minute.
Congratulations.
It's delicious.
I'll be right back.
Just a little later.